If you open up the documentation, you can see a
couple of examples of typical screen widths. Then it suggests how
you can setup your layout folders, so that you can
have a different mean activity layout for tablets versus for handsets.
And here we define tablets as having a smallest width
of at least 600 dp. To customize the UI further, we
can create a layout-sw720dp folder. That way, we can have a
different main activity layout for ten inch tablets versus for seven
inch tablets versus for handsets. So back to
our quiz. We need to define activity_main.xml file in
our base layout folder so that we can accomplish
this layout on the phone. This layout applies to
both phone, portrait, and landscape, so we don't need
a special version of the layout in the layout
lan folder. We do also need to declare activitymain.xml
in the layout-sw600dp folder. That way it will override
the one pane UI and use a two pane UI in this case. It will be
picked up on devices that have greater than
600 gp in both width and height. That
means seven inch and ten inch devices in
both portrait and landscape mode. And lastly, we
don't need layout-sw720dp because we don't have different
layouts for seven inch versus ten inch devices.